=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 5=
Are you ready for it?
Wait, Yu Ming.
I've only decided
not to divorce you for now.
You don't have to...
You...
I... You didn't even bathe.
It's so messy here.
Is this
money?
I ran it through a bill counter.
It's all real.
I knew this would happen.
I thought
you'd fall back.
Unexpectedly,
you fell face down.
Where did you get all that?
It was hidden in the wall.
One of the walls was hollow inside.
Got it from the wall?
No need. I'm fine.
You are so tough.
You're much more sober than I was.
When I found the money,
I passed out on the spot.
Then I woke up, saw the money,
and passed out again.
Over and over,
I don't know
how many times I blacked out,
or for how long.
How much in total here?
30 million.
Does Hong Jinkui know this?
No.
If he knew,
why would he sell me the house?
Does the former owner know this?
No.
I went to see her.
She said everything about this house
had nothing to do with her from then on.
Her own words.
Do you have...?
Yes.
You mean this?
♪Every fortune♪
♪Has its cause♪
♪Do not mistake it♪
♪For heaven's grace♪
♪Lost in pleasure♪
♪Blind to sorrow♪
♪The lure of gold lights♪
♪The path to ruin♪
♪A fleeting taste of wealth♪
♪A carefree dream♪
♪Neon lights flicker♪
♪Minds drift astray♪
♪Wine runs dry♪
♪Another night is gone♪
♪Yet life's burdens♪
♪Remain unresolved♪
♪A dream of fame and fortune♪
♪Blinds the hearts of many♪
♪Life's endless scenes♪
♪Pass in the blink of an eye♪
♪A fleeting taste of wealth♪
♪A carefree dream♪
♪Neon lights flicker♪
♪Minds drift astray♪
♪Wine runs dry♪
♪Another night is gone♪
♪Yet life's burdens♪
♪Remain unresolved♪
♪A dream of fame and fortune♪
♪Blinds the hearts of many♪
♪Life's endless scenes♪
♪Pass in the blink of an eye♪
I had a dream.
Me too.
So thirsty.
I'll take a sip too.
I'm a little hungry.
If we go crazy like this,
will you get pregnant?
It doesn't matter. Just let it be.
With the money,
we can have as many kids as we want.
But how do we explain this?
We can't put it in the bank.
Right?
Making multiple deposits won't do.
It'd trigger warnings from the bank.
Yeah.
Just say
it was passed down
and was dug out at home.
Did your ancestors use RMB notes?
We dug out some gold ingots
and sold them.
What floor do you live on?
The second floor.
Can you dig there?
No.
Borrowed it from a friend.
Oh sure, you happen to have a friend
with 30 million.
This won't work.
Let's do this.
We move the money back home first.
If we took so much money home,
would your mom handle it,
or would my mom?
Don't let the excitement kill them.
What can we do then?
We can't bring our money back home.
It's like wearing fine clothes at night
when no one can see.
What a shame!
Let's get more sleep.
Just have another dream.
Miss Zhou, you know her?
Chen Zinuo,
my classmate at the University of Music,
Drama and Media Hanover in Germany.
Back in school,
we liked competing for the top grade.
Sometimes, she ranked first,
and sometimes, I did.
But she always outshone me.
My advisor said my efforts
couldn't match her natural talent.
No matter how
technically accurate I was,
I could never
interpret the music as deeply
as she did.
So, sometimes,
even when I won,
I wasn't happy.
I always felt like
she was letting me win.
Wait here for me.
Why are you here?
I sent you many messages.
Did you read them?
I just want an answer.
Back then, I was ready
to go to Paris.
But Dresden State Orchestra
suddenly sent me an offer.
Did you give that chance to me?
Your scores were better than mine.
I didn't need you to give it to me.
All these years, I always thought
you were a principal cellist
at some orchestra.
What are you doing here in this place?
What's wrong with this place?
Music can just be played
anywhere.
You can play it at a hotel,
at an orchestra,
at the beach,
in the desert, or by the sea...
You can even play it on a plane.
Is there a problem?
Let's go.
Let me.
Okay.
Thanks.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
Just be happy yourself.
Am I right?
It's late. I'll hail a cab for you.
I've never
ridden a motorcycle before.
♪Sunlight falls through the curtains♪
♪Softly kissing your face♪
♪Like a secret♪
♪A little secret♪
You want to take this motorcycle?
♪Whenever we're together♪
♪It's the perfect time♪
♪A little understanding♪
♪Our bond growing deeper♪
♪When I look into your eyes♪
♪I see the stars shining♪
♪Listening to your heartbeat♪
♪Such a special rhythm♪
♪I'm falling for you♪
♪Now baby I love you♪
♪And I just need you too♪
♪Every second♪
♪Every minute, every day♪
♪I want to be by your side♪
♪The moments that steal my heart♪
♪Choosing where to have dinner♪
♪Or staying in all day♪
♪That's okay♪
♪Even our little disagreements♪
♪Are part of our love story♪
Thanks.
♪Never letting go♪
You're welcome.
♪Through every changing season♪
Bye.
♪We've written a story of our own♪
♪And I still remember our promise♪
♪To explore the world♪
♪Together♪
♪Now baby I love you♪
♪And I just need you too♪
♪Every second♪
♪Every minute, every day♪
♪I want to be by your side♪
♪The sweetest moments♪
Dad,
why do you take me here
to play the cello?
I hope you can feel
that music is not limited
to time
or space in this world.
No matter where it is played,
it can be furious,
joyful,
remorseful, or sorrowful.
Because you and your cello
are both free.
(Song Youcheng)
(Sorry.)
(The number you dialed is busy now.)
Not coming to work,
not asking for leave,
and not answering the call.
What's this?
Rebelling?
Among so many people,
no one could even lead
this tour group.
Mr. Song,
it's not that no one can lead them,
but Tong has led
this senior tour group before.
They said they were really happy
with Tong leading them.
That's why they have added
so many add-ons.
They specifically asked for Tong.
You may leave now.
Keep calling her.
If that doesn't work, go to her place.
Got it.
My master is a veteran employee
at our agency.
It's normal for her
to have a bit of a temper.
After all,
sometimes, we need her
to push for performance, don't we?
What?
Could such a big travel agency
not run smoothly
without Wen Yitong?
Mr. Song, please calm down.
It's not that this matter
can't be solved.
I'll lead
this group.
Last time my master
led this group, I was with her.
I know full well
how to make
these old people happy.
For something my master
can't bring herself to do,
I can do it.
For something she can
bring herself to do,
I can do it too.
You truly have a honey tongue
and a heart of gall.
I don't actually hide my "gall."
I'm
open
and aboveboard.
(Wen Yitong)
You want to get fired, huh?
You didn't answer my calls
or reply to my messages.
And you're absent without leave.
What time is it now?
Just you wait.
You'll know the consequences
when you come.
I don't need to wait.
You wait there.
I'll go see you.
Crazy.
This woman is insane.
She actually hung up on me.
Tong.
Master,
the group gathers at the Ferry Square.
Move aside.
Song Youcheng!
I quit!
Have I been too lenient with you?
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you've caused me?
Serving people is exhausting.
I'm done. I quit.
Why put on airs now?
Who doesn't serve people?
I do, too!
Let me tell you,
if you can't reach the top,
we're all the same,
just serving others.
Fine, even if you did reach the top,
when you were climbing up,
you'd only see their butts.
Only when you reach the top
and look down
do you see smiling faces.
Go on!
Go find
a job not meant for serving people.
Let me know when you find one.
I'll follow your lead.
Putting on such an act with me!
You're really full-fledged, huh?
I'm not only full-fledged,
but I've also found my backbone
now.
Are these
called turtle eggs?
Put it down!
I won't take it.
Who'd want your turtle eggs?
I'm blessing you now.
May they hatch sooner,
the group gathers at the Ferry Square.
I'll put it here safely.
Keep it warm.
Bye-bye.
- Master...
- Don't do this.
Your nails are quite pretty.
Don't break it.
Don't follow me.
Wait. Let me take a breather.
Take a minute before we go.
(Jiari International Travel Agency)
This place can be seen as
the starting point of making ends meet.
(Jiari International Travel Agency)
I just went step by step
without stopping.
I even rubbed the skin off my heel.
It healed later.
Then rubbed off again,
then healed again.
In my bag or drawer,
there are always some Band-Aids.
I bought those top-tier ones
that don't curl up at the edges.
They stick on really tight.
Later, calluses developed on my heels,
and I felt no more pain.
Jia said I had subdued
those shoes.
Fan Meijuan always reminds me
to be content with my life.
I feel content.
Even when I had no money
in my pocket,
I still felt content.
A 15-yuan bowl of noodles
is no different from a 150-yuan one.
A 30-yuan bag
and a 300,000-yuan bag
would just contain similar things,
like tissues and stuff.
I used to think like that.
Now, there's 30 million in my house,
but I still think that way.
What's this called?
Yu Ming,
that's called a poor man's mentality.
After graduating from college,
I told myself,
"I'm going to live a rich life."
Just a few years have passed,
yet I was smoothed out
and tamed by life.
I got subdued.
When you are used to being poor,
suddenly becoming rich
would just make you feel at a loss.
You don't know what to do.
You panic, getting all flustered.
If you're willing,
you can transform into anything.
Like the Monkey King,
who has 72 transformations.
Let's go.
Let me take you to let off some steam.
This shop looks nice.
Not bad.
Pick something.
This is men's wear.
This one.
This set looks good.
May I try this on in a size L?
I'm sorry, Miss.
Our new employee
has hung it in the wrong place.
It's fine
if it's the wrong place.
Get her a size L to try on.
Yeah.
Sorry, sir. It's unavailable.
What about size M?
None of that, either.
Wait, what size is that set?
It's size L.
Well, what do you mean?
Here is the thing, sir.
Our brand has a regulation.
Your total expense
must reach 200,000
to try those kinds of outfits on.
200,000?
Did you have to emphasize it that much?
Just go get it.
It's you, Yitong?
Let her try it on.
Ms. Wang.
You came too.
Why are you here?
Just bring it over here.
Sorry, sir.
Our company has a regulation.
Only VIP members
can purchase the new-style items.
I don't think
you're qualified for this right now.
What about this?
Am I qualified to purchase it now?
Can I become a VIP?
Wait, what's going on here?
Now, people are spending money this way?
You can't do business like this.
No.
I don't want it anymore.
I don't like that outfit.
It's no big deal.
I'm a VIP of your shop.
Which one did she want to try?
That one is ugly.
That khaki color.
I don't like that outfit.
I don't want to buy it.
It's fine. Let her get it for you.
It's no big deal.
Go get it for her.
Ms. Wang...
Yitong!
Look at you.
You have no idea
how to do business.
You are so mean like this.
Well, haven't you
lost a key account?
Our company has a regulation.
What regulation?
You are just stupid.
This way,
you've lost a key account.
Sir...
Please introduce your items to me.
Is there anything new?
I thought you went to the toilet.
That salesgirl is so mean.
She
was picking on us.
But I scolded her.
Did you put the money safely?
It's safe here.
She has lost a key account.
Let me tell you,
we're reeking a kind of smell now.
What smell?
The smell of poverty.
We'll get rid of it with money then.
Continue our 72 transformations.
♪Rolling in cash♪
Comfortable?
Too small.
It doesn't matter.
There are bigger ones.
Pack them all.
Bro,
you have no idea.
It was a bag full of banknotes.
A sea of red!
Wen Yitong's foolish husband
just poured it all on the table.
A large pile, you know.
He was forcing them
to take it.
He must have been chosen
by the God of Wealth.
I was wondering why she chose to quit.
She has really
climbed to the top of the pyramid.
I can't see anything.
Something must be hidden inside.
Otherwise, why would he
seal the windows?
Bro.
Look,
what's that?
A bill validator.
Weijie,
are you done?
Right away. Well...
I need to make a call first.
Hurry up. It's too hot.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
(Cousin Qian Weijie)
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
Hello.
Yu Ming,
where are you?
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'm taking my kid out for some fun.
But my car broke down on the way.
Bring some tools
and come help me fix it.
I won't go.
I'll cover your fuel cost.
I'll transfer 200 yuan to you.
Is that okay?
I'll give you 300, but I won't go.
Are you being
rebellious with me today or what?
I just won't go!
I didn't make it perfect,
did I?
You didn't sound decisive enough.
Yeah.
I wanted to let off some steam to him.
But as I was often
being ordered around by him,
I was suddenly at a loss for words.
It's fine. You'll get better gradually.
I, Monkey King,
have intimidated the Heavenly court
in an imposing manner.
No one dares to challenge
the Golden Cudgel
with unstoppable force.
Battle drums sound above the clouds.
I will turn the world upside down.
What are you doing? Let's go.
I want to invite Aunt's family
to dinner.
Okay.
Hello, Mom.
Yu Ming wants to invite us
to dinner this evening.
What else could it be for?
It must be because
he feels guilty towards me
and wants to make up for it.
Fine,
we'll head straight to the restaurant
in the evening.
Okay.
What's up, darling?
Who's treating us to dinner?
Yu Ming
wants to treat our family to dinner.
He said it's not spacious
enough at home,
so he wants to dine out.
Yu Ming is treating us?
And we're dining out?
What show is he putting on here?
Elegant Garden?
That's right. Elegant Garden.
Waitress,
may I ask
where the Ascension Room is?
Go straight ahead,
then up the spiral staircase
to the second floor.
This place
is known
for 1,000 yuan a bite.
Mom,
could he plan
to borrow money from us?
Treating us to dinner
without even getting the money?
That's not something Yu Ming would do.
Could he
have joined
a pyramid scheme?
I heard
those people would
pretend to be very rich
in the beginning.
They'd say there are
piles of money at their place
and they could make millions a month.
Just their lies.
Once you join them,
you'd get ripped off.
So,
later,
when we're in there,
we must keep our minds
sober.
Let their words go in one ear
and out the other.
Got it?
Mom, don't worry.
How could we be fooled
by that slow-witted Yu Ming?
You can't be too careful.
Yeah.
Let's first go in to see.
Are the dishes gorgeous enough?
Really gorgeous.
Well,
how much for this table?
Have you checked the bill?
No, I won't check it.
This way, please.
Oh, my gosh!
This is insane!
Ming,
you're inviting us
to such an expensive place to eat?
Auntie, don't make a fuss over it.
Please take a seat.
Please.
I'm inviting you here today
just to have a decent meal.
It's no big deal.
Uncle,
you can sit wherever you want.
Aren't your parents coming?
No, they won't come.
They'll come next time.
Yeah.
That won't do.
Ming, they should come.
I'll call her right away.
Your mom,
in her whole life,
has never dined
in such a place.
Well...
Just don't call her.
We'll have dinner together another day.
Yeah, we had a plan for it.
Let's come together next time.
Yeah.
Yitong,
your earrings are so shiny.
Did you
go to a formal event today?
You're wearing such a decent outfit.
Is this decent? Just something casual.
Just casual wear.
Y-Yu Ming,
if you've got something,
you can just tell me
on the phone.
Now, here in Elegant Garden,
you arranged this table of dishes.
It's really unnecessary.
It's necessary.
For you two,
in the latter half of the year...
Yeah.
Your daughter
Wenwen's tuition fees
are super high.
Yitong
has to work very hard, right?
I just...
Like this...
I just wanted to treat you to dinner.
I don't believe it.
If you want to take a loan,
I tell you,
it's impossible.
Because you're not
even qualified.
You just can't remember that.
We're not taking a loan, Weijie.
Throughout my life,
I'll never take a loan from you.
I... I invited
everyone to have dinner today
just to enhance
our emotional bonds as relatives.
I know
these years, you might had
some misunderstandings
about our personal development.
I just want to say
that since we're relatives,
there's no need for us
to make a scene
every time we dine together.
Everyone has their dark days.
I want to say
that what goes around
comes around.
Right?
It's right to say what goes around
comes around.
But for some people,
things just go around.
That's fate.
You must accept it.
What do you think?
Let's eat.
Uncle, please eat.
Let's eat. Right?
Don't say those useless things.
What about wine?
No wine, no party. Jie,
go fetch the wine from our car.
No need.
We'll just order the wine here.
My dad only drinks fine wine.
The wine here isn't cheap.
It doesn't matter if it's expensive.
Waitress,
bring us
a case of the most expensive wine.
Sure, please wait a moment.
Bring it bottle by bottle.
Bring more when we're done.
Please enjoy.
(Think bigger)
So pleasant.
Let's drink the pleasant wine, too.
Waitress,
two more bottles.
Here, Dad,
let me pour it for you.
Yu Ming.
Darling,
don't just lie there like that.
Why is it...?
Why is it pinching his finger?
Come on.
You...
Get up now.
Let's have a drink.
Well, he really can't hold his liquor.
With just these few cups,
you got drunk like this?
Before drinking this,
I'd like to say something.
Today, you...
Well...
Look,
these dishes you ordered
are a bit out of line.
And you were out of line
on the phone, too.
But
since you're one of our own,
I just won't hold it against you.
But I have to remind you
that you can't be like this
when you are out there.
You can be useless.
But you can't be
arrogantly useless.
Yu Ming,
I've said so much
just for your own good.
I'm your brother.
Don't just call me by my name.
Okay?
Let me say something too.
I know
you all look down upon me.
All these years, I've been
at your beck and call.
The reason why I just bore it all
without losing my temper
was that
when my brother passed away,
you helped our family.
When my mom was sick,
my aunt
bought medicine for her from abroad.
And you remember
Wenwen's birthday every year.
I'm very grateful to you.
But I want to tell you
that everyone
can have further development.
I won't just let things go around.
Drink it up.
Weijie, don't drink like that.
Look closely.
This is for the candied hawthorn
I licked
when we were little.
This is for your headset,
broken by me.
This is for breaking
or scratching
your porn DVDs.
There's more.
It's fine.
Let me see
whether the money is genuine.
I-i-is it genuine?
It's genuine.
So much money!
Where did he get all that money?
Look.
It's him.
As far as we know,
Mr. Yu, the lottery winner,
(A lottery buyer won 130 million)
has always been a strong supporter
of the sports lottery.
He's been buying
lottery tickets for ten years.
This outfit,
Mind has an identical one.
Totally the same.
Though before this,
he never won a grand prize,
Mr. Yu thinks
purchasing sports lottery tickets
can not only contribute
to the public welfare undertaking
but also can buy himself...
I also bought a ton of lottery tickets.
Why didn't I win a grand prize?
Having a pipe dream again?
From the winning ticket,
you get 130 million.
There'll be dozens of millions left
after tax deduction.
You might lose it all
by failing your business.
Then you'd owe the bank 130 million.
What's this called?
A sudden fortune would bring disaster.
Think about it.
Even if you become rich,
what can you do?
Live in luxury villas, buy luxury cars.
Every day, you're here
moving luxury cars in and out.
Haven't you had enough of it?
You should know
that buying a luxury car is your dream,
but selling luxury cars
is your true distant goal.
What are you standing there for?
Get moving!
Rush towards your distant goal!
After claiming the prize,
the same afternoon,
Mr. Yu went to the local
charity foundation
and donated four million
for public welfare,
letting this windfall
bring warmth to society.
Winning the lottery is his luck.
Donating the money shows his true class.
Yu Ming?
Let's congratulate Mr. Yu
on winning the prize again.
That's Yu Ming!
It really is Yu Ming!
Contribute to society.
Well,
Yu Ming has drunk too much.
I'll send him back first.
You guys go on eating.
I'll settle the bill.
Yitong,
I've paid the bill.
Well,
I've put the money back.
If you think the dishes here are good,
we'll come next time.
Yeah.
(Signature: Qian Weijie)
Good thing we changed our clothes back.
You got drunk and might
ruin your clothes by throwing up.
Weijie was so strange.
Why did he compete to pay the bill?
He shouldn't have.
Did he suddenly grow a conscience?
When did he ever have a conscience?
Moreover, his conscience
isn't worth 30,000 at all.
Has he been stunned
by your bragging words?
And he believed it?
That shouldn't be.
Working at the bank,
he must have seen
much of the world.
Darling, do you think he has
found out about our money?
So...
It shouldn't be.
He can't possibly know it.
How could he know it?
This is just so strange.
Their whole family acted weirdly.
They were so arrogant
when they showed up.
Why did they suddenly
change their attitude?
Yu Ming.
Yu Ming,
I'm talking to you.
Let's analyze this a bit.
Good dishes and wine are so expensive.
I have no luck in enjoying them.
I threw it all up.
You're so pathetic.
I'm truly impressed.
Don't bend your neck like that.
Or you just lie down.
Darling,
take me to have some satay noodles.
To nourish myself a bit.
♪I want to get rich♪
(Hong Jinkui)
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
♪Fancy cars, pick what I want.♪
That's 130 million!
Oh, my god!
How long can someone spend it all?
Mom,
it's impossible for him
to give it all to us.
At least, he should give us
half of it.
If you ask me,
don't go see
that 130-square-meter apartment.
It's second hand,
and it's not located in a good place.
Better consider the one in Haicang Bay.
Big penthouse in an affluent area.
Four bedrooms, two living rooms,
and two bathrooms.
When the baby is born,
it'll be spacious enough.
We'll check that one tomorrow.
Dad,
your mindset is lagging
behind the times.
Look, house prices are so high now.
There's just no room for appreciation.
You've got to put the money in my hands.
I'm a professional
in financial management.
Enough.
Have you forgotten how much
you've lost in the stock market?
If you ask me,
our family's money
should be managed by me.
If you let me keep the money,
it would be the safest.
I seldom spend money.
I can keep it safe.
Cut it out!
Look at the pile
of those
health supplements.
All fake goods.
If the money
is in your hands,
sooner or later,
those fraudsters will
scam you out of your money.
Qian Lai,
I've married you
for over 40 years now.
Today, I finally
see your true colors.
Enough.
Everyone, stop talking.
Let me tell you,
without my permission,
no one can touch
this money.
What does she mean?
She means she'll keep all the money?
Let me tell you, Qian Weijie,
it was your family
who begged me
for this second child.
Now, your whole family is ganging up
against me.
Let's just call it quits.
I'll take Zihan away,
and you can't see our second baby.
Just live your own days.
Jie,
I think
it's best
to let me keep the money.
I've always been
very reliable.
Where are you going?
I'm buying some cigarettes.
He's out of his mind.
Bill validator.
And there are two of them.
Gosh.
How much money could they have?
If there's really
nothing important in Unit 505,
why is that couple
staying there?
The villa is full of garbage.
Yu Ming acted all sneaky.
He sealed the windows
and changed the lock.
His wife fighting with him is now back.
All this shows
the money
is right in Unit 505.
Shall we
test the waters when it's still dark?
We can't.
The surveillance system
was upgraded last time.
Now, it's facial recognition.
Strangers would trigger an alarm.
Truly a high-end community.
But we just have to find a way
to sneak in.
A thousand-mile quest
for the dragon's path,
where every encircling peak
is a hidden gate.
What does it mean?
Dig a hole.
Get up quickly.
You'd sleep a full 24 hours
if you continued.
I'll lie here a while longer.
Why did you drink with them
so heavily?
Don't you know
your capacity?
That was fine wine.
It's over 10,000 a bottle
at Elegant Garden.
How could I let them drink more
than I did?
However expensive it is,
didn't you throw it all up in the end?
What you threw up
in the end wasn't that wine,
but the satay noodles.
You're just fated to eat satay noodles.
But it was fine.
Fine wine doesn't make you
feel so awful.
Look at this.
Bought it on a whim.
What's this? A turtle shell?
It's pretty.
Can I even go out wearing this?
Sure, you can. It's not out of place.
Look at this.
If I'm wearing these,
I'd have to practice how to walk.
I want to return
all this stuff.
Why?
We still don't know
the origin of the money.
I just feel insecure
after spending so much
all at once.
It has no origin.
Understand?
It was found in our house,
so it's ours.
It's a gift from heaven.
Why feel insecure?
I'll return them all.
I'll keep none of them.
I must return them all.
Return them all?
Would the salesperson beat us?
The salesperson...
Coming!
Who is it?
Auntie, you're at home.
You are...
It's me, Jie.
Qian Weijie.
When Ming and Yitong got married,
I offered you a toast.
You don't remember?
Qian Weijie?
When was that?
Did you remember it?
Why didn't you tell me
that you had come?
I would've thrown you a welcome dinner.
I've brought gifts for you,
Ming, and Yitong.
This is black tea
meant for our bank's key accounts.
Please try it.
If you like it, I'll bring you more.
Ming is not up yet?
Ming, get up now.
I've brought you
an electric razor.
I tried it. It works great.
So I bought you one.
Yitong,
a gift for you.
Ya
has just bought a Tote bag.
The tag is still on it.
She says it's very big
and can fit a lot.
It would suit you perfectly.
Come on, get up.
Get up.
Get up to look.
Wenwen, you're here.
Here.
I know
you love snacks of this brand.
I bought this specially for you.
Come on, take a look.
It's too sweet, cloying.
Wenwen,
don't you like drawing pictures?
I happen to know
a curator.
I'll have him
hold a painting exhibition for you.
How about it?
Something's off.
The meal last night cost 37,000.
37,000? So expensive!
He covered the bill.
Why?
How could I know?
Let's go out to check it out.
Let's put on our clothes first.
Ming,
how about you deposit that money
with me?
What money?
Next Episode
(Actress, Ren Suxi)
I'm Ren Suxi.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
You won such a huge lottery prize.
Who would not know?
You won 130 million!
Ming, Yitong,
you two are truly blessed.
So, you shouldn't pay the property fees.
I will cover them.
Your status is different now.
Things have changed.
We are your relatives.
It's your personal ride.
Are you forcing it on me?
No charge.
Just take it for a spin.
Just checking if I'm dreaming.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪